Ordering From Canada?  

ORDER NOW

Privacy Policy
==============

**LAST UPDATED: APRIL 24, 2020**

This notice describes the Privacy Policy of E. Mishan & Sons, Inc. (“Emson”) and is effective as of the date Last Updated. By visiting this site, providing information through this site, and/or purchasing a product from this site, you are consenting to and accepting the terms, conditions and practices described in this Privacy Policy.

We may collect information that identifies you individually or allows us to contact you directly (personal information). We may ask for or collect personal information when you purchase a product, request a service, request refunds, returns, and exchanges, submit a review, subscribe to communications, respond to a survey, or engage in some other activity on our site. We may ask you for contact information such as your name, address, telephone number, and email address. We may ask you for geolocation information, or it may be automatically provided by your browser or device. If you do not want Emson to collect geolocation information, you can turn off location services in your browser or device.

When you visit our website, to the extent permitted by law and applicable agreements, we may collect site visitation data information such as your IP addresses, IMEI/UDID, MAC address, browser type, operating system, pages visited on our site, referring and exit pages, the dates and times of the visits, and the terms that you use in searches on our websites. We may partner with certain third parties to collect and analyze some of this information for permitted business purposes. Emson may use this information to improve site administration, provide general statistics, or for any other purpose permitted by law. This information may be linked with other personal information to the extent permitted by law.

We may obtain data about individuals from third party sources, such as financial information, credit history information from credit bureaus, search term and search result information. Emson may use this information to provide better service to you, or for any other purpose permitted by law.

We may use the collected personal information to fulfill and provide the products, services, or information you request from us, for processing refunds, returns, and exchanges, tracking and confirming orders, marketing and advertising products and services, conducting research and analysis, administering various programs, or for other lawful business purposes. This may include sending information that you have requested or contacting you about products and services that you have purchased. We may also share information with affiliates and third parties so that they may contact you by email, postal mail, or phone regarding products, services, promotions, special events, or other subjects that we think might appeal to your interests.

We may combine the personal and other information we receive from one source with information we receive from other sources. For example, we may combine personal information collected through our websites with other information that we collect about you in other contexts—such as our communications with you via email or phone, or your customer service records. We also may combine your personal information with information that we obtain from third parties.

If you do not opt-out of communications from us, we may send you marketing notices including promotions of our products and services. Emson or a third-party provider will process opt-out requests within a reasonable time. [Click here](https://emsoninc.com/unsubscribe/) to unsubscribe.

We may employ third parties to perform functions on our behalf including order fulfilment, delivering packages, return processing, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, conversion of abandoned shopping carts, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments and chargebacks, and providing customer service. We may provide collected personal information to third parties as needed to perform their functions. Emson may sell, rent, trade, or otherwise share collected personal information with third parties for promotional use.

Emson sites and promotional emails may use technologies including trackers, cookies, web beacons, clear gifs, action tags, and/or location-based services, which may result in the collection of personal information. Emson may use this information to track system usage, to assist in tracking and analyzing advertising effectiveness, including for email campaigns, to count and recognize site visitors, to personalize your experience, to conduct general analysis and research, to personalize advertising, or for any other purpose permitted by law. Our sites may not be designed to respond to "do not track" requests from browsers.

We may release account and other personal information when required by law, regulation, court order, subpoena or other legal process, or when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; to enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Emson, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Emson may use a tool called Google Analytics Advertising Features, which may include Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting, integrated services that require Google Analytics to collect data for advertising purposes, including the collection of data via advertising cookies and identifiers and/or the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration. These features if enabled allow Google Analytics to collect data about your traffic via Google advertising cookies and identifiers, in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation.

Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting and may also make use of other Google Analytics for Display Advertising tools, including Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting and/or the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration. You may opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising by using the Google Ads Settings page. You may also prevent your data from being collected and used by Google Analytics by opting out through the use of the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. If Emson makes use of the Google Analytics for Display Advertising Remarketing feature, Emson will use such Remarketing feature to advertise online, and third party vendors, including Google, may show Emson ads on sites across the Internet. Emson and third party vendors, including Google, may use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on a user’s past visits to Emson, and/or report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to Emson. Data from Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting may be utilized by Emson to help recognize and understand user preferences, to make improvements to Emson’s digital operations, to choose content and advertising to display to you, and for other business purposes as permitted by law and any applicable agreements.

Emson does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 16. While this Site is a general-audience website, Emson does not sell products for purchase by children. We may sell children's products for purchase by adults.

When you use a social media suggestion function on the site, we may ask for a friend's name and email address. We will use this information to automatically send the specified email message to the friend. We may retain the information you provide for tracking purposes.

We use cookies to help us improve, promote, and protect our services. By using the site, you agree to our cookie policy. When you visit our site, a cookie may be saved on your computer (if your computer accepts cookies), and if you return to the site the cookie may be read. We use cookies to help us collect the site visitation data described above and in some cases to deliver specialized content. A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Some parts of our website may use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. We may use this information for any purpose permitted by law.

Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you prefer not to receive cookies on our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser. Refusing cookies or turning them off may have unpredictable effects on the functionality of the site.

Our website may contain links to other websites. If you use these links, you will leave our website. When you access a non-Emson website, even one that may contain the Emson logos, please be aware that we do not control the content and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of that site. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of those websites linked to our website, which are outside of our control.

Our website may include social media features such as the Facebook "Like" button, or the "Share This" button. Social media features on this site collect standard information such as your IP address, the page you are visiting on our website, and may use cookies. Social media functions provided by a third party are governed by the party’s privacy policy.

We use reasonable physical, technical and administrative security measures to protect the personal information that we collect, however, we cannot guarantee and do not warrant or represent, that all information will be protected against loss, misuse, or unauthorized access by third parties. By your use of this site, you acknowledge that no Internet data transmission and no means of electronic or physical data storage can be guaranteed as secure from such incidents and agree that you will not hold us responsible for any breach of security. You acknowledge that we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you use this site at your own risk.

We may retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We may share personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution, or similar event.

**CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS**: If you are a resident of California, Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code gives you the right to request certain information with respect to the types of personal information we share with third parties for direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom we have shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. To request a copy of the information disclosure, please contact Emson toll free at 800-423-4248.  Additionally, please see our California Consumer Privacy Act Disclosures concerning rights you may have under the California Consumer Privacy Act.  In the event of any inconsistency between the California Consumer Privacy Act Disclosures on one hand and the Terms and Conditions and/or Privacy Policy on the other hand, the California Consumer Privacy Act Disclosures control.

Special note for individuals outside the United States: The personal and other information that is subject to this policy (including the information collected on Emson sites from visitors outside the United States) is collected and controlled by E. Mishan & Sons, Inc. in the United States. Emson’s principal office is in New York, New York. You agree that your information will be processed in the United States for the purposes described herein. As described above, Emson also may subcontract the processing of your data to, or otherwise share your data with, Emson affiliates, authorized distributors, trusted service providers, and trusted business partners in the United States or countries other than your country of residence. The data-protection laws in these countries may be different from, and less stringent than, those in your country of residence. You expressly consent to such transfer and processing.

Any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Terms & Conditions, including limitations on damages, limitations on warranties, mandatory arbitration, and application of the law of the state of New York. Our Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions may change from time to time. Our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have or may collect in the future about you and your account.

We may from time to time update this Privacy Policy in our sole discretion. When we make these updates, we will change the "last updated" date listed at the top of the Policy.

Copyright © 2024 Granitestone Stackmaster. All rights reserved.
